www.1000fr.net presents
Sync:FRS@Ììô¥ °²Äȸâ201419
True Detective S01 EP01
REC
What'd you think,
you paired up with him?
Louisiana State Police CID
Statement of: HART, Martin Eric
What'd I think?
May 1st, 2012
Well, you don't pick your parents,
And you don't pick your partner.
You know, they used to call him
The Tax Man for a while?
He'd come out of Texas,
so nobody knew him.
Seemed a bit...
Raw-Boned to me, edgy.
Took 3 months till we got him
Over to the house for dinner.
Around our big 419.
That's what y'all
want to hear about, right,
Dora Lange, kids in the woods?
Yeah, sure, but, uh,
talk about Cohle.
We heard some stories.
Kind of a strange guy, huh?
Strange. Uh-- Heh, heh, heh.
Yeah.
Rust would pick
a fight with the sky
If he didn't like
its shade of blue,
But when we finally got
him over to the house--
This is when that case was hot--
Poor bastard looked
like he was on his way
To the firing squad.
Dora Lange.
Yeah. Occult ritual murder.
Louisiana State Police CID
Statement of: Cohle, Rustin Spencer
You can thank the
"Advertiser" for that.
April 26th, 2012
- Could you, uh, hold off on that?
- All right. Yeah. You can't do that here no more.
- Huh?
- Uh-Uh.
Don't be assholes.
You want to hear this or not?
Vermillion sheriff
requested assistance with a 419,
Cane fields outside of Erath.
I'd been on the job
about 3 months till then.
Two previous cases
were open and shut.
It was January 3, 1995,
my daughter's birthday.
I remember.
Hart and Cohle, State CID.
Who found her?
Farmer and his son.
This spread wasn't
scheduled for a burn.
Let's keep them here,
and let's tape off this road,
And give me your log.
- You take the log.
- Yes, sir.
Make sure you get everything down.
Go ahead.
You ever see something like this?
No, sir, in 8 years of CID.
Them symbols, they's Satanic.
They had a "20/20"
on it a few years back.
ID?
No, sir.
We're gonna need more men
for a grid search,
Set up a perimeter wide
as possible on those 3 roads,
Post up, take license plates
Of anything that passes.
I-23.
Go ahead, I-23.
We're gonna need investigator
assist on that 419,
All you can spare for a canvass.
- Roger that, Detective.
- CID is taking over.
- Okay. Tell me what you see.
- Get anybody who's free up here.
Ligature marks on her wrists,
ankles, and knees.
Multiple shallow stab
wounds to the abdomen.
Hemorrhaging around throat,
Lividity at the shoulders,
thighs, and torso.
She'd been on her back a while
Before he moved her.
That's why they called
him The Tax Man.
The rest of us had these
little note pads or something.
He had this big ledger.
Looked funny walking door to
door with it like the tax man,
Which ain't bad as
far as nicknames go.
Yeah. Of course I've always
taken a lot of notes.
I mean, you never know what
the thing's gonna be, do you?
A little detail somewhere
way down the line
Makes you say, "Ohh!"
Breaks the case.
You know, I've seen
all the different types.
We all fit a certain category--
The bully, the charmer, the, uh,
surrogate dad,
The man possessed
by ungovernable rage,
The brain--
And any of those types could be
a good detective,
And any of those types
could be an incompetent shitheel.
Which type were you?
Oh, I was just a regular type dude
With a big-Ass dick.
A lot of it had to do with
how they manage authority.
There can be a burden in
authority, in vigilance,
Like a father's burden.
It was too much for some men.
A smart guy who's
steady is hard to find.
I was all right,
better than some,
But, you know,
I knew how to talk to people,
and I was steady.
Rust-- Now his Texas
files were classified
Or redacted,
and he wasn't big on talking
Except when you
wanted him to shut up,
But he was smart.
Yeah. Second week
we were together,
I saw where he was living.
Kind of made me feel for the guy.
I'd offer you a seat, But, uh...
Don't mention it. I,
uh-- I can't stay.
Yeah, I'll tell you guys--
And believe me,
past a certain age,
A man without a family
can be a bad thing.
We'd encountered
a meta-Psychotic,
Which I had to explain to Marty,
What meta-Psychotic was.
This is gonna happen again,
Or it's happened before, both.
Go on.
It's fantasy enactment, ritual,
Fetishization, iconography.
This is his vision.
Her body is a paraphilic love map.
How's that?
An attachment of physical lust
To fantasies and practices
forbidden by society.
You get that from
one of your books?
I did.
Her knees are abraded,
rug burns on her back.
Cold sores, gum line recession, Bad teeth.
There's decent odds
she was a prost.
He might not have known her, but...
This idea goes way back with him.
You-- You got a chapter
in one of those books
On jumping to conclusions?
You attach an assumption
to a piece of evidence,
You start to bend
the narrative to support it,
Prejudice yourself.
Wait and see on the ID.
All right.
This kind of thing does
not happen in a vacuum.
I guarantee this
wasn't his first.
It's too specific.
Listen, uh-- Ahem, this is A...
Stupid time to mention this, But...
You've got to come to dinner.
Can't put Maggie off anymore,
So you just got to.
All right.
- Gordon, thanks for coming.
- Marty.
Yeah. So...
Anyway, that evening,
wasn't even sundown,
He decided it was a good time
to invite me over for dinner,
Which I got a problem with,
All right, because I'm
thinking about Marty's wife
And this two kids and how
it's my daughter's birthday,
And I know...
There's nothing I can do about it,
Maybe not today,
maybe not tomorrow, but...
I'm gonna have a drink.
- Let me get up! Heh, heh!
- Daddy!
You're gonna meet him.
I got to get the door.
Hey.
Santa Claus is coming!
Aah! Jump! Ha, ha, ha!
People out here,
It's like they don't even
know the outside world exists.
Might as well be living
on the fucking Moon.
There's all kinds of
ghettos in the world.
It's all one ghetto, man,
Giant gutter in outer space.
Today, that scene,
That is the most fucked
up thing I ever caught.
Ask you something?
You're a Christian, yeah?
No.
Well, then what do you got
the cross for in your apartment?
That's a form of meditation.
How's that?
I contemplate the
moment in the garden,
The idea of allowing
your own crucifixion.
But you're not a Christian.
So what do you believe?
I believe that people shouldn't talk
About this type of shit at work.
Hold on, hold on.
Uh... 3 months we been together,
I get nothing from you.
Today, what we're into now,
Do me a courtesy, okay?
I'm not trying to convert you.
Look. I consider myself
a realist, all right,
But in philosophical terms,
I'm what's called a pessimist.
Um, okay. What's that mean?
Means I'm bad at parties.
Let me tell you.
You ain't great outside
of parties either.
I think human consciousness
Was a tragic misstep in evolution.
We became too self-Aware.
Nature created an aspect of
nature separate from itself.
We are creatures that should
not exist by natural law.
Huh. That sounds
god-Fucking-Awful, Rust.
We are things that labor under
the illusion Of having a self,
This accretion of sensory
experience and feeling,
Programmed with total assurance
that we are each somebody
When, in fact, everybody's nobody.
I wouldn't go around spouting
that shit, I was you.
People around here
don't think that way.
I don't think that way.
I think the honorable
thing for species to do
Is deny our programming,
Stop reproducing,
Walk hand in hand into extinction,
One last midnight, brothers and sisters
Opting out of a raw deal.
So what's the point of
getting out bed in the morning?
I tell myself I bear witness,
But the real answer is that
it's obviously my programming,
And I lack the
constitution for suicide.
My luck, I picked today
to get to know you.
3 months, I don't hear
a word from you, and--
- You asked.
- Yeah.
And now I'm begging
you to shut the fuck up.
I get a bad taste in
my mouth out here.
Aluminum, ash,
Like you can smell
the psychosphere.
I got an idea.
Let's make the car a place
of silent reflection From now on,
okay?
?????
What should I bring for dinner?
A bottle of wine
would be nice, I guess.
I don't drink.
Well, no, of course not, Rust.
Listen. When you're at my house,
I want you to chill the fuck out.
Don't even mention any of that
bullshit you just said to me.
Of course not, Marty.
I'm not some kind
of maniac, all right?
I mean, for fuck's sake.
- What'd you hear?
- Ask Cohle.
You mean The Tax Man?
You know, he's IA.
This is State CID Homicide-
- Detective Geraci.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm calling to ask
about that night...
I mean, you never heard any
shit like this before.
She had...
Antlers. Um...
Fuck.
This is-- This is the real thing,
Some "Halloween" shit.
Well, we're gonna have
to do a press conference.
What about him?
What do you think?
Smart...
Aloof.
Doesn't care about
making friends,
But he's already
running with it.
He's got a real--
Real mind for it.
Yeah.
So you'd keep him on then?
Both of us, yeah. I would.
All right. You're still lead.
The incident room is yours,
And, uh, you do
the briefing tomorrow.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Hello, sir.
Fuck that prick.
- Yeah. No. I couldn't hear you there.
- Antlers and shit.
That's my point,
I wanted you to see her.
Yeah, you don't mark
up a body like that...
She had antlers?
What does that mean?
It was a crown.
We'll do the briefing
tomorrow, guys, early.
My guy does the AP
Wire asked about Satanism.
It got Speece here.
You're gonna have his nose up your ass.
Major was saying something
about a press conference.
Well, guess I can count
my blessings, fellas.
Thanks for that.
Hey. You mind if I skate? Ahem.
I got some names
from Vice, prost farms.
Check around on our DB.
You want me to go with you?
Nah. Just something to do.
Yeah. You go ahead.
I'll take care of the paperwork.
Like I said, I'm feeling a lot of stuff
Hit me at this time--
My daughter's birthday,
this dead woman,
And, um...
Figured I'd work
the case, you know,
Till DiCillo called
or we got an ID.
State Vice gave me some
addresses to follow up on.
So far, nobody'd--
Nobody'd talked to me.
Evening, ladies.
I was hoping to ask
y'all a few questions.
Oh, come on, man.
I'll get the next round.
Heh. You making trouble for us then?
No. I'm just looking to
get some information On a woman.
Might be you know her.
- Who's that?
- Hold on.
We'll take two large Long
Island ice teas, please.
Ma'am.
I'm Rust, by the way.
I'm Anette, she's Lucy.
Either one of you know a woman
About your age,
works the same place,
About 5'5", blond like you?
What kind of tits she have?
Medium, a little larger than yours,
Proportion to the body natural.
Gee. I don't know. We see a lot
of girls Like that around.
Any girls like that
You haven't seen around
lately, missing like?
People come and go.
What do you want them for?
I wouldn't bust
somebody for hooking
Or drugs.
I'm murder police.
Somebody got killed.
There's a girl named Liza,
Another called Destiny,
But I seen Destiny
yesterday at McDonald's.
What about Liza?
She's here.
Anette, go get a couple more drinks
From the bar, will you, please?
All right.
You get pills pretty easy?
Relax. I want some.
Speed?
No. Quaaludes, anything-Barbital.
Uppers are easier to get,
And they last longer, too.
Yeah, but it's not like that.
What's it like?
I don't sleep.
Hey.
Hey, Lone Ranger.
Dreaming.
Why you out here, huh?
Why didn't you come to bed?
Caught a... bad one yesterday.
Just couldn't sleep.
You got that woman from Erath?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Saw it on the news.
Girls will be up soon.
Missed you the last couple days.
Oh, shit. I got to shower.
Got a debriefing today
And maybe a press conference later.
And if Speece calls,
Tell him I'm debriefing
the squad all morning.
Well, Marty said he was doing that.
He is.
Hey, beautiful.
Morning, baby.
Marty, how you want
your coffee, doll?
Strong and black just like you.
Prints came back. Dora Kelly Lange.
Priors for shoplifting,
possession, and...
Solicitation.
Address outside of St. Martinville.
Landlord says she hasn't
lived there in almost a year.
She's got an ex Charlie Lange,
Who's doing 8 in Avoyelles for bad checks,
Mom's outside of Breaux Bridge,
DMV license expired,
And DiCillo called.
She was washed clean,
Not a print on her.
We got ligature marks
on the wrists and ankles,
Was bound by a half-Inch rope,
Maybe 10, 20 hours.
Evidence of vaginal intercourse.
Bound upright,
Hadn't eaten in a day, maybe more.
Toxicology hit for lysergic
acid and methamphetamine.
That's crystal and LSD.
How much LSD?
Hard to say.
Got to wait for a mass spec.
So she was drugged, bound,
Tortured with a knife,
Strangled, posed out there.
Yeah.
What about this stuff?
Well, the crown,
for lack of a better word,
Rose thorns, early cane,
switchgrass Wrapped
around a bent branch,
And the horns are deer antlers.
Again, no prints on anything.
Symbols are painted
with acrylic basic blue
Using a thick glove finger.
Ideas what any of this means?
I don't know.
And it's all primitive.
It's like cave paintings.
Maybe you ought to
talk to an anthropologist.
Lot of trouble this guy went to.
Seems real personal.
I don't think so.
Was iconic, planned...
And in some ways, it was impersonal.
Think of the blindfold.
This place is like
somebody's memory Of the town,
and the memory's fading.
It's like there was never
anything here but jungle.
Stop saying shit like that.
It's unprofessional.
Oh, is that what
I'm going for here?
I just want you to
top saying odd shit,
Like you smell a psycho's fear
Or you're in someone's
faded memory of a town.
Just stop.
Well, given how long it's taken for me
To reconcile my nature,
I can't figure I'd forgo it
on your account, Marty.
You get any sleep last night?
I don't sleep.
I just dream.
Occult.
Now, I don't know if this
shit is anything but crazy,
But Speece and
the Superintendent,
They're paying attention,
the newspapers are making hay,
Church groups.
Detective?
All right, here's
what we got so far.
Deceased's name is
Dora Kelly Lange, 28...
You stay busy now, the business?
Well, yeah, I got
the security firm,
PI stuff. Routine.
Lotta guys leave the job,
Cemetery within 10.
No family, idle hands.
Some advice, you make it out,
you stay busy.
Hit the corners.
Ask about anybody
she was seeing...
Regular customers, meth dealers,
And rough johns, anything.
Any questions?
You believe in ghosts?
What'd we say about
silent reflection?
You happen to hear
anything out of the ordinary
Between 10 and 1 AM, out back?
No, no, but, uh,
Sometimes they, uh,
dove-Hunt out there.
They found a woman?
Is it the Fontenot girl?
Who?
- And why would you ask that?
- Don't know.
Went missing around
here years back.
Last time something happened.
Just thought maybe it's her.
How old was she, this girl?
I don't know. Little.
You know where the family lives?
Had a place couple streets down.
They moved out, though.
Do you know the Fontenot girl,
one went missing?
Her?
Her family come to our service
Once or twice, 5 or 6 years back.
Is that the girl? Oh, Lord.
No, sir, it's not.
Excuse me.
I want to ask y'all something.
Y'all think Maybe this have
something to do with those cats?
What cats?
Two of 'em-- One, and a couple
Of weeks later, another.
Somebody cut 'em up,
Turned their insides out,
then nailed them To the front door, twice.
Now, I called and told the police,
But we're predominantly
African American congregation.
I asked for it to be investigated.
We're not those type of police, sir.
Well, who is, then?
Can I ask you something?
Any of these look familiar to you?
- Seen them anywheres?
- No.
No, they look like something that might be
Carved into a tree or something.
Mm-Hmm. How about these?
Now, that look like
something my old auntie
Taught us how to make
when I was a tyke.
What are they?
Some folks call them bird traps.
Old Auntie told us that
they were devil nets.
You put them around the bed,
catch the devil before he get too close.
That's interesting.
- Hmm.
- She was a wonderful woman.
Loved her some Jesus,
but had a bit Of that
Santeria in her, you know?
I always just thought it was something
For children to do, keep 'em busy,
Tell them stories why
they're tying sticks together.
Then that's all we got
on the Fontenot girl.
There was nothing in there.
Says, "Possible
report made in error."
Now, that was 5 years ago.
Ted Childress was
sheriff back then.
He's set up in Gulf
Shores now, I think.
Ten-Year-Old girl goes missing
and that doesn't go state-Wide?
Now, hold on now.
My understanding,
The little girl went off
with her birth daddy.
Now, did you check
her mom's record?
Possession, solicitation.
I believe Ted knew the family,
and the feeling was The little
girl was better off with her daddy.
Mom seemed to agree;
she filed a complaint,
Then never bothered with it again,
Took off with her boyfriend.
R&I said you had a complaint
these parts Around December--
Little girl Getting
chased through the woods.
Oh, yeah, I pulled that
one for you, too.
What the hell is this?
Little girl said a
green-Eared spaghetti monster
Chased her through some woods.
Now, we had her work
with a sketch artist,
And she told us that
looked exactly right.
Now, you want to call an APB on that,
you go right ahead.
Listen, boys. I'm gonna have to
call a timeout, make a beer run.
Well, why don't you hold
off on that for a while?
All right, well,
why don't you get it, then?
We really don't
want to do that.
Well, is this supposed
to be admissible? Huh?
If you want to pick my brain,
work a room,
You buy me a cheeseburger
and a Coke, don't you?
I'll take a sixer of Old Milwaukee
Or Lone Star, nothing snooty.
Why is this so important
to you all of a sudden?
'Cause it's Thursday
and it's past noon.
Thursday is one of my days off.
On my off days,
I start drinking at noon.
You don't get to interrupt that.
I'd appreciate a
little hustle up on that.
Yesterday,
At approximately 6 AM,
Civilians came across
the body of a female
In a sugar cane field
outside of Erath.
Now, this person,
we believe, was murdered,
And we are not yet
in a position to
Release the identity
of the victim
or to offer Details
of the crime.
Our investigators
Have several leads,
and hopefully we'll--
We'll have a suspect
for you in custody soon.
Now, this perpetrator
Will be apprehended, and he
will know Swift Louisiana justice.
how old was she?
- Charlie?
- Mm-Hmm?
Let's talk about
your ex, Dora Lange.
You want to talk Dori?
What's she said I've done now?
Nothing. We're just
curious if you knew
What she's been up to and
maybe where she's living.
Nope.
Got her divorce papers pushed through
After I been here about a year.
I don't blame the bitch.
She got a habit?
Yeah, a few.
Weed, meth, juice.
Name it.
Charlie,
How'd y'all meet?
Growed up together,
dropped out the same time.
Hitched up way too quick.
You know how it is--
You want a wife, but only half the time.
- Hmm.
- Why are you saying you hadn't heard from her?
She called up here for
you not too long ago.
She couldn't help me anyway, man.
She sounded all fucked up.
You see, that's exactly
the kind of thing
That we do want to know about,
though, Charlie.
Oh. All right.
Uh... I needed some
scratch for my store,
And Dori owes me money,
she ain't got no fuckin' phone,
So got a number
to her friend Carla,
got her To call me back,
and she ain't made no fuckin' sense.
Carla's full name
and phone number.
What you mean,
she didn't make sense?
Like she could
duck-Hunt with a rake.
High, yeah.
Talkin' 'bout she's
gonna become a nun.
- Why a nun?
- I don't know, man. She was high.
Fucked up,
uh, Talkin' 'bout...
she met a king.
Shit.
Anyway...
I don't need no snitch
jacket up in here.
Give me a break.
This is Avoyelles.
It's a goddamn day camp.
Spend some time in Angola.
Surprised you even
got Aryan Nation here.
What'd Dori do?
Dori's dead.
Thank you, boys.
We almost had a moment there.
So you want to talk the
whole case through or just the end?
No, whole story From your
end, you don't mind.
You know, like he said,
files got ruined.
Hurricane Rita.
What he didn't say is that
this is about something else.
Something new. That one
in Lake Charles, maybe?
Now, why you say that?
Get the details out of the paper.
Yeah, we did.
You know anything about that,
about Lake Charles?
Well, let me see What you got,
jog my memory.
Well, let's hear
your story first,
See how it fit with what we got.
Well, your dime, boss.
Talking Cohle,
what about that dinner
You mentioned, he turn up drunk?
Oh. Yeah.
Well, ahem.
That dinner,
that was a bit later.
It was kind of funny.
The flowers, you know?
Like, he read somewhere that
if you get invited to dinner,
You're supposed
to bring flowers?
The hell?
You can barely stand up.
What is it?
You don't drink with me or the boys,
And you got to get a load on
Before you visit my family?
No, Marty, it's not like that.
And I didn't mean to,
All right?
And I don't drink 'cause I've
had trouble With it before;
I didn't mean to.
I was checking on a CI.
I ended up hanging around a bar.
I was sitting there.
I couldn't think of a good reason not to.
Usually I can.
Don't worry about it.
Have some more coffee And just try
to make 10 minutes of conversation.
You got it.
I'll call Chris or somebody,
Get you out of here.
Marty.
I'm sorry, man.
Forget it.
We'll try this some other time.
Well, uh, Rust, it is
so nice to finally meet you.
Sorry it took so long.
Well, I tried to tell her
you aren't big on socializing.
I said that your life's
In this man's hands, right?
Of course you should
meet the family.
Well, not quite as
dramatic as that, hon.
I've never fired my gun.
- Have you fired your gun?
- Audrey.
Yes.
- You shot people?
- Macie.
Dad's never shot anybody.
Well, that's good.
You don't want to shoot people.
But you have.
Marty says you're from Texas.
Yes, south Texas.
I grew up in Alaska.
Just been working here
the last 10, 12 years.
What kind of work?
Narcotics, mostly.
Was on the Robbery Squad
in Houston until '89.
Ahem. Oh. Be right back.
Y'all keep eating.
Do you like your job?
Not exactly,
But it's worthwhile.
I'm good at it.
You're not married?
Once.
- Uh, not anymore.
- Mm-Hmm.
Did you do this while
you were married?
Hey, Chris.
Hey, thanks for the page.
Yeah, well, he'll appreciate it.
Well-- all right,
then I appreciate it.
Children?
One.
She passed.
Marriage didn't last
long after that.
Sorry.
Chris Demma's
on the phone for you.
Something about a CI or...
Back there to the left.
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
What was that?
What were y'all talking about?
Your job.
What do you know
about him, Marty?
Um, not a lot.
He could be a good detective.
He's running on this
thing, but, uh...
uppity.
What?
Jeez. Have you ever
asked him about himself?
Baby, trust me.
You do not want to pick
this man's brain.
What was that?
Oh, some details
on the CI.
Thank you for dinner, Maggie.
- This looks great.
- My pleasure.
I don't like that broccoli.
Mind your manners.
So you, uh, need to go or what?
No, it's nothing can't
wait till tomorrow.
Rust, uh, what
you were saying before?
Oh, we can find something
nicer to talk about.
Marty, I saw
your table in there.
You fly-fish?
Little bit.
So you
and Cohle went bad in '02, huh?
Heard about that.
Yeah, well... what happened
between me and him
don't have nothing to do
with Dora Lange.
I worked with Rust Cohle
for 7 years.
People change.
Relationships change.
You stay in touch?
No.
No, I haven't talked
to Rust in...
10 years.
Yeah.
Look, however we...
he was a good detective,
and it don't matter how
he ended it. I mean...
I can say that
because it's the truth,
and I don't hold grudges.
I believe that's the shit
that leads to cancer.
But why am I talking
about dinner?
Y'all want to walk through
the Lange case, fine.
This other stuff--
well, what's going on?
Sorry. We just heard
some stories.
Well, personally, I heard he was
an ace case man, right?
I'd like to understand
his process.
"His process."
Sure.
The other landlord
says she trashed the place,
so she lost her deposit.
And the neighbors check out.
Those that remember her
said that she, uh,
used to come in early
in the morning,
if she came home at all.
You guys canvass the bars
pretty good today?
You know, up your ass, Cohle.
Why don't you do your
own fuckin' leg work,
you rat fuck?
Say it again, rummy.
You know what, man?
Fuck you,
Tax Man.
What the fuck?
Back to point.
Got 3 hits on working girls.
No one close to her, naturally.
A few names recognized
her as occasional.
Like she tricked
now and then,
show up at a couple of truck stops
when she needed cash.
You got some names.
Which ones?
I heard from my AP guy,
Ray Fontenot.
Said her uncle's
Danny Fontenot--
the pitcher, LSU.
Yeah, I watched him
play. Great player.
Well, he lives close by.
Well, thanks, guys.
What about you two?
Did you get anything today?
- Not much, sir.
- Well...
You might know
the Reverend Tuttle.
He runs our state-wide
charity drive.
This is Detective Hart,
Detective Cohle.
Pleasure to meet you, Officers.
Nice to meet you.
Cohle.
Your case has a lot
of people taking care,
doors locking where
they used to not.
Eddie's been speaking
to me about it.
Concerned, very concerned.
We've been discussing
the viability of a task force
to investigate crimes with
an anti-Christian connotation.
You what?
Really?
Yes.
I don't mean to tell men
of your positions,
but there is a war
happening behind things.
Thank you for doing your part.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
Well...
Eddie's going to be very, very pleased
to have such good men working on this.
Are you kidding me?
Un-fuckin'-believable.
"Anti-Christian."
Fucks. And who
the fuck's Eddie?
Is he serious?
Well, he doesn't
have a television.
- Who's Eddie?
- And he's from Texas.
He's the fuckin'
governor--
Edwin Tuttle.
They're first cousins.
Well, that makes sense.
Yeah, that's the
sound of The Big Machine,
Cohle, that's gearing up
to pound your ass.
The sound of a gaggle of hens.
Yeah, you better
watch your mouth
or they're gonna
peck your eyes out.
I am looking for
Detective Hart.
I have a stack of
depositions for him.
Judge Sutpen told me to
make sure and give them
to Detective Hart
and no one else, so...
Is that the, um--
The, uh, depositions.
I thought I should
walk you through them.
Oh. Great, great. Let's
just find a place to talk.
Thanks, Cathleen.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Right through here.
Your victim was Dora Lange,
but you all checked
on Marie Fontenot. Why?
Missing girl, 5 years gone,
report made in error?
She had an uncle
who lived nearby...
and call it intuition.
Sometimes he's more responsive.
I'd like to help.
Mr. Fontenot all the way.
We met,
oh, maybe 7 years ago.
I was visiting Skip Hays.
I'd played for USL.
Thing of beauty, sir,
watching you throw.
Danny, this man's a detective
with the police.
I'm actually--
Ahem. Sorry, uh,
we wanted to ask you
about your niece, Marie.
"How much could You put on
one family?" I ask the Lord.
We try to get by.
Did you know Marie's
birth father?
Len?
Len Stroghes was her daddy.
It's okay.
We're asking because, uh,
we had heard that Marie
ran off with him and that...
she wasn't
really missing.
That's what Debbie said.
Oh. Well, uh...
anybody heard from Len?
Anybody maybe knows
where he's at?
Uh, sorry.
The last thing.
Do you know
where Debbie is now?
She married another man.
Not the one she's
with when Marie...
She was in Vegas,
last we heard.
Marie must have loved it here.
Yeah.
All this for her?
Danny loved her so much.
We weren't her legal guardians,
but she played here
all the time,
more than her Mama's.
I can see why.
What is it Dan has,
if you don't mind my asking?
All they ever told us was
"a cerebral event."
Series of strokes, like.
Marty?
Excuse me for one sec.
Inside on the floor
on the right.
I don't know what that is.
I haven't looked in there
since the police first came.
Bet you want
to hear the hero shot, huh?
That place we carried
the kids out?
Eventually, sure.
So what did she look like...
that one in Lake Charles?
Can you, uh, tell us
anything about that, Mr. Cohle?
That looks a lot
like the one from '95,
but... well,
you knew that already.
Yeah, there are specifics
consistent to the '95 case,
details that weren't
public knowledge.
You were off the grid
for 8 years, right?
- Show back up here 2010.
- My question is--
How could it be him...
if we already
caught him in '95?
How indeed, Detectives?
I figured you'd be
the one to know.
Then start asking
the right fuckin' questions.
Join our FRS/FRM and have fun!
QQ Group No.77207643/frzhaopin2@gmail.com
welcome to www.1000fr.net